>> Brian Holt: 现在所有这些都是我想给你看的
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now that all of that
is working together I wanna show you
有些想法给你一些很酷的想法你现在可以做了
some like, give you some ideas of really
cool stuff you can do now that you have
访问所有 CSS 和 JavaScript。
access to all the css and JavaScript.
这就是一个很好的例子。
So, a good example of that would be here.
这是所有 JavaScript ，所以我可以为所欲为。
This is all JavaScript, so
I can do whatever I want.
我可以说， >> Brian Holt: Const 颜色
I could say like,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Const color
我不知道现在我们可以用粉色
equals I don't know, for
now we can make it like, pink.
在这里，这是一个模板字符串，对吧 ?
And then here,
this is a template string, right?
所以我可以把 #333 放进去，把颜色放在那里，对吧 ?
So instead of having #333 there, I can
just put ${ and put color there, right?
>> Brian Holt: 看起来好一点，不是吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That looks
marginally better, doesn't it?
现在你可以看到你的线了，那看起来是粉红色的。
Now you can see your line, well,
that looks really pink up there.
但我的电脑很漂亮
But it's very nice looking on my computer.
你能用 JavaScript做的任何事
So, anything that you
can do with JavaScript,
现在你也可以在这里做了
you can now do in here now as well.
所以我可以做点什么让它发挥作用
So, I can do something like,
make this a function really quick,
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And say return,
>> Brian Holt: 让我们在这里做个挂钩
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's just make a hook here
真正快速的常量填充 =
really quick const padding =
useState >> Brian Holt: And
useState
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
这里我们说初步填料是 15吧
here we'll say the initial
padding will be 15, right?
>> Brian Holt: 并设置填充，并在此处放置填充。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And set padding,
and we'll put padding here.
然后在这里的标题上
And then here, on the header,
只要有人点击
anytime that someone clicks,
加填充加 15 或
to setPadding of padding plus 15 or
就像这样
something like that.
这会让我们心烦心乱这不是件简单的问题
It's gonna be upset cuz this is not
a quick cuz this is not element, but
我们只是来举个例子
again we're just here for examples.
所以现在如果我刷新这个， >> Brian Holt: 我们的背景色，
So now if I refresh this,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Our background color,
动物/p 背景色填充，我希望它只是填充。
animal/p background color padding,
I want it just to be padding.
>> Brian Holt: Padding，这可以是， >> Brian Holt: Pink。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Padding, this can be,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Pink.
>> Brian Holt: 我在这里搞砸了什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: What did I mess up here?
好的好的
Yeah, okay.
那么现在，如果我点击这个，请注意我每次点击它的时候，
So, now, if I click this,
notice that every time that I click it,
它变得更加美丽和美丽
it gets more beautiful and more beautiful.
看他们会接吻的
Look, they're gonna kiss.
[ LAUGH] 如果我的设计师妻子能看到我
[LAUGH] If my designer
wife could see me now
她就会杀了我直说吧
she would just murder me,
just straight up.
但我要指出的是这真的很酷
But the point stands here that this is
actually pretty cool that I commend it
以编程方式处理样式，对吗 ?
manipulate styles programmatically
like this, right?
这和 css 的关系有点难
This would have been a bit more
difficult to do with css and
JavaScript 是非常独立的，对。
JavaScript being very separate, right.
但因为我们把一切都聚在一起了
But because we've mashed
everything together,
我们对我们的东西有很大的控制
we get a lot of control over
what our stuff looks like.
>> Brian Holt: 有任何问题吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Any questions about that?
>> Brian Holt: 如果要在生产应用程序中使用此产品，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If you want to
use this in your production app,
我给你设计的这个设计是值得欢迎的，就把它给我吧。
this design that I've made you
are welcome to, just attribute it to me.
这就是我想要的
That's all I want.
>> Brian Holt: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay.
> > Brian Holt: 所以让我们来做我们的， >> Brian Holt: Poodle 稍大一点，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's make our,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Poodle a little bit bigger,
所以我要把 css equals css之类的
so I'm gonna put css equals css,
like that, and
我要我们的狮子狗要做字体 60px 之类的
I want our poodle to be font-size 60px,
something like that.
> > Brian Holt: 所以我刚刚补充说，就在那，现在我们该过去了，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I just added that, right
there, and now we should go over here,
我们的狮子狗应该很开心
and our poodle should be nice and happy.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，就在那部分， 17 到 19。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, just out of that
part right there, 17 through 19.
所以，我不会说这不是为了大家，对吧 ?
So, again, I'm not gonna say if
this is not for everyone, right?
有些人只会发现我们甚至会考虑
Some people are just gonna find this
atrocious that we would even consider
把这些东西都放在一起
putting these things all together.
但是让我给你几个好处
But let me give you a couple of
benefits beyond what I've shown you
有计划的方面
with the programmatic aspects of it.
如果我删除了 navbar ， CSS 就会用它，对。
Now if I ever delete navbar,
the CSS goes with it, right.
因为所有 CSS 都建在这个 navbar上。
Because all the CSS was
built into this navbar.
你们中有多少人在网站上工作只有 2 兆字节的 CSS
How many of you have worked on websites
where you just have 2 megabytes of CSS and
你主要使用的是 10% 但你不知道你能删除什么
you're primarily using 10% of it but
you don't know what you can delete.
我当然是对的
Me certainly me right.
当我加入 LinkedIn 时， LinkedIn 有 2 兆字节的 CSS。
LinkedIn when I joined LinkedIn
we had 2 megabytes of CSS.
谁知道我们到底在用多少钱，对吧 ?
And who knows how much that we
were actually using, right?
所以我喜欢用词组优化删除能力，对吧 ?
So I like to use the phrase optimize for
delete ability, right?
因为如果您要优化可删除的代码，那么如果您的代码是可删除的，
Because if you're optimizing for
deletable, if your code is deletable,
这就意味着它是模块式的对吧
that means it's modular, right?
你可以把它拉出来整个塔都不会倒塌
That you can pull pieces out and the whole
tower doesn't come tumbling down.
这也是一个很大的好处。
So that's a big benefit as well.